// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is correct about constants vs variables in PHP?",
    answer: " Both of the above",
    options: [
      "Constants may be defined and accessed anywhere without regard to variable scoping rules.",
      "Once the Constants have been set, may not be redefined or undefined.",
      " Both of the above",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following function is used to locate a string within a string?",
    answer: "strpos()",
    options: [
      "search()",
      "locate()",
      "strpos()",
      "All of the above"
      ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following method acts as a constructor function in a PHP class?",
    answer: "define",
    options: [
      "const",
      "define",
      "constant",
      "#pragma"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is the way to create comments in PHP?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    optioens: [
      "//commented code to end of line",
      "# commented code to end of line",
      "/* commented code here */",
      "All of the above"
      ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What does PHP stand for?",
    answer: "PHP: Hypertext Preprocessor",
    options: [
      "Preprocessed Hypertext Page",
      "PHP: Hypertext Preprocessor",
      "Hypertext Markup Language",
      "Hypertext Transfer Protocol"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a valid PHP comparison operator?",
    answer: "<=>",
    options: [
      "!=",
      ">=",
      "<=>",
      "<>"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: " What is the strpos() function used for?",
    answer: "Both b and c",
    options: [
      "Find the last character of a string",
      "Search for character within a string",
      "Both b and c",
      "Locate position of a stringâ€™s first character"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is array_keys() used for?",
    answer: "Returns all the keys of an array",
    options: [
      "Compares array keys, and returns the matches",
      "Returns all the keys of an array",
      "Checks if the specified key exists in the array",
      "Both b and c"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is Joomla in PHP?",
    answer: "An open source CMS",
    options: [
      "Set of library enriched with fucntions",
      "An open source CMS",
      "Framework for designing dynamic pages",
      "Framework and distribution system for reusable PHP components"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the default execution time set in set_time_limit()?",
    answer: "30 secs)",
    options: [
      "20 secs",
      "30 secs",
      "35 secs",
      "40 secs"
    ]
  },

];